<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seminar on Air-Sea Modeling Lab. Yonsei Univ.</title>
    <link>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/categories/seminar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Seminar on Air-Sea Modeling Lab. Yonsei Univ.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2020 [ASML Yonsei](https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr) All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:21:46 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/categories/seminar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Seminar at Hanyang University</title>
      <link>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/news/hanyang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:21:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/news/hanyang/</guid>
      <description>한양대학교 해양융합과학기술 인재양성팀 초청세미나 Hajoon gave a talk with the title &amp;ldquo;The Southern Ocean where the ocean and atmosphere meet &amp;ldquo; at Hanyang University</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEES Colloquium</title>
      <link>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/news/sees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 23:57:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/news/sees/</guid>
      <description>SEES Colloquium at Seoul National University Hajoon gave a talk in the SEES Colloquium with the title of &amp;ldquo;The ocean circulation and its impact on the air-sea CO2 exchange&amp;rdquo;. He introduced the offline experiments with carbon cycle and emphasized that near-inertial waves can give a significant influence on the CO2 flux through vertical mixing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 기상학회 기후분과 봄 학술대회</title>
      <link>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/news/kms_climate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 23:57:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/news/kms_climate/</guid>
      <description>2019년 한국기상학회 기후분과 봄학술대회 
송하준 책임연구원은 2019년 한국기상학회 기후분과 봄학술대회의 학생워크샵에 강사로 초청되어
&amp;ldquo;해양물리의 관점에서 보는 탄소순환&amp;rdquo;
이라는 주제로 강연을 하였습니다. 많은 분들이 참석하셔서 모두 같이 해양물리와 탄소순환이 어떻게 연결되어 있는지 알아보는 의미있는 자리였습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seminar at Ewha Womans University</title>
      <link>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/news/ewha/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 23:57:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/news/ewha/</guid>
      <description>The Colloquium at the Dept. of Climate and Energy Systems Engineering Hajoon gave a talk about the changing climate in the Southern Hemisphere with the title, &amp;ldquo;The Southern Oean where ocean and atmosphere meet&amp;rdquo; in the Department Colloquium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seminar at KOPRI</title>
      <link>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/news/seminar_kopri/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 23:03:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/news/seminar_kopri/</guid>
      <description>A Visit to Korea Polar Research Institute Hajoon was invited to the EGG seminar at Korea Polar Research Institute in Incheon. The talk was titled &amp;ldquo;Seasonal Variation in the Correlation Between Anomalies of Sea Level and Chlorophyll in the Antarctic Circumpolar Current&amp;rdquo; and discussed the impact of mesoscale mixed layer depth modulation on chlorophyll along the Antarctic Circumpolar Current in the Southern Ocean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seminar at NIMS</title>
      <link>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/news/seminar_nims/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 23:03:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/news/seminar_nims/</guid>
      <description>A Visit to National Institute of Meteorological Sciences Hajoon visited National Institute of Meteorological Sciences in Seoguipo, Jeju Island, and gave a talk with the title of global and regional physical ocean data assimilation and a strongly coupled data assimilation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seminar at Korea Meteorological Administration</title>
      <link>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/news/seminar_kma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 22:57:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/news/seminar_kma/</guid>
      <description>A Visit to Korea Meteorological Administration Hajoon visited Korea Meteorological Administration and gave a talk about the analysis and application of the ocean model.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>