<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Research in ASML on ASML-Yonsei</title>
    <link>http://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Research in ASML on ASML-Yonsei</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="http://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Air-sea Interaction</title>
      <link>http://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/research/airseacouple/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 07:49:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/research/airseacouple/</guid>
      <description>Air-sea interactions     We are investigating air-sea couplings to understand the climate system in both large- and meso-scale processes. For the research, we are using a coupled atmosphere-ocean model with biogeochemical module and explore the physical processes and their impact on biogeochemical processes including the carbon cycle.
Air-sea CO2 exchange     While investigating the role of mesoscale eddies using both observations and numerical models, we find quite complicated, yet very interesting impacts of eddies in the Southern Ocean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ocean Circulation</title>
      <link>http://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/research/southernocean/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 07:49:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/research/southernocean/</guid>
      <description>Southern Ocean     The Southern Ocean is unique. Consistent eastward wind results in upwelling of the water from the interior of the ocean, providing a passage for the exchange between the atmosphere and deep ocean. Unlike other major ocean basins, it does not have boundaries so that water circulates all around Antarctica. This wind-driven current is called Antarctic Circumpolar Current (ACC) and flows eastward connecting Atlantic, Pacific and Indian Oceans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State estimation</title>
      <link>http://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/research/dataassimilation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 07:49:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://airsea.yonsei.ac.kr/research/dataassimilation/</guid>
      <description>California Current System     The California Current System is located at the east of the north Pacific. Equatorward upwelling favorable wind draws nutrient-rich water from the interior to the surface making ocean very productive. In fact, approximately 35% of wild-caught fish come from here (Kudela et al., 2009). I investigated the interaction between wind, upwelling and marine ecosystem using ocean circulation model.
Upwelling source waters     Along the California coast, equatorward wind transports water to offshore, creating divergence and upwelling at the coast.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
